getitbazaar.com 2016-02-11

# Online Shopping India:Shop Clothing,Bags,Shoes,Watches Online in India

This document is published in accordance with the provisions of Rule 4(1) of the Information Technology (Reasonable security practices and procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules, 2011 which requires the publishing of a privacy policy for handling of or dealing in personal information including sensitive personal data or information. 

Getit Stores, AskMeBazaar is a brand name of Getit Stores Private Limited, a company incorporated under the provisions of the (Indian) Companies Act, 1956, having its registered office at 8B, Bahadur Shah Zafar Marg, 1st Floor, ITO, New Delhi -110002 (hereinafter referred to as **"Getit Stores"** **"we"** **"us"** or **"our"** ). 

Any reference to "you" or "your" in this privacy policy (" **Privacy Policy** "), means you as a user of our site [http://www.AskMeBazaar.com](http://www.askmebazaar.com/)) (" **Site** "), or any other portal as may be lauched by Getit Stores  including you availing any of our online services available on the Site such as buying and selling of merchandise/tangible products (" **Products** "), as a seller and/or buyer (" **User** "), advertising and such other services as may be included and modified from time to time (together referred to as " **Services** "). 

As a User, your access to and use of the Site is conditional upon your acceptance of and continued compliance with this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and all rules, guidelines, policies, terms and conditions applicable to a Service and/or Indirect Service being provided by Getit Stores (" **Policies** "), as may be modified by Getit Stores from time to time, unconditionally and at all times and further agree and confirm that you consent to providing Getit Stores information about yourself for the purpose set out below and you understand that such collection, storage and handling is lawful, necessary and permissible under applicable laws.

Each capitalized term not defined but used in this Privacy Policy shall have the same meaning as ascribed to such term in the Terms and Conditions _(defined below)_. ****

**1.                   ****Requirement for collection of information**

The information collected is relevant and necessary to understand you or your online shopping preferences, order history, processing payment and for support and facilitation of your buying activities. The information is collected with an intention to provide you with a customized site experience, provide updated information, related transaction information, provide latest information on offers, carry out follow ups, to assist with customer service or technical support issues, troubleshoot problems, collect receivables, measure gauge for surveys on your interest in the products available, inform about online and offline offers, products, enforce the Terms and Conditions and other related policies or to prevent fraud and unlawful use. It may be noted that Getit Stores has strict guidelines with respect to unauthorised access to information provided by the User (as enumerated below). ****

**2.                   **Collection of Information

Our **Privacy Policy**  contains provisions regarding collection, storage and handling of personal and non-personal information that you share on the Site. These could include mandatory or voluntary disclosures that you make while and for using the Site. Personal Information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person ( **"Personal Information** **"** ). Personal Information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy shall include, but not be limited to, your name, address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, e-mail address, etc. provided by you whilst using the Site and/ or availing the Services.

By accessing, browsing and continuing to use/browse the Site or by clicking on "Register" or "Submit" icons or other relevant icons/ buttons on the Site, or by placing on order for any Product, you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, and the fact that we store and process your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

What we know about you we get mostly from you.  But we may also have to find out more about you from other sources in order to verify the information submitted by you, and to make sure that what we know about you is correct and complete.  This kind of verification is primarily done in order to address various security concerns, and to ensure that you comply with the provisions of applicable laws, and the terms and conditions available on the Site (" **Terms and Conditions** ") and other terms and conditions as may be prescribed by us from time to time.  We do not collect personally identifiable information (including Personal Information) about you, expect when you specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. ****

**3.                   ****Usage of Information Collected**

Getit Stores is sensitive towards your information including your Personal Information and non-personal information (email, demographic location and address, age, name, phone number, clothing sizes, payment details etc.) provided at the time of registering with Getit Stores or otherwise while availing the Services and/or Indirect Services on the Site. ****

We use information about you to help us provide you with a more personalized service which is tailored to suit your needs.

Your personal information may be used by us to:

(i)                 monitor, develop and improve the Site, Services and your experience;

(ii)               assist in and administer the provision of Services to you;

(iii)             process and deal with any complaints or enquiries made by or about you; and

(iv)             investigate any suspected breach of the Terms and Conditions  or the breach of other terms and conditions otherwise relating to you and to monitor compliance including by way of checking postings or submissions to the Site.

Where and only where requested/agreed by you, we will:

(i)                 send you and keep you updated with information by email, telephone (including SMS) or mail about existing and new services and special offers from us;

(ii)               send you information by email, telephone or mail about related products or services of selected third parties that may be of interest to you; and

(iii)               use the information for marketing and for market research purposes, including internal demographic studies, to provide, optimize and personalize our services and to send you newsletters and information about our products and services.

The information is readily available on the Site and only viewable by you by logging on to the Site. You, at all times have the option not to provide any personal or other information about you without agreeing to register with Getit Stores and otherwise withdraw your consent by communicating the same to us in the manner in the Terms and Conditions and the Policies. Upon withdrawal Getit Stores will have no obligations towards you nor will it be liable for the Services and products provided till the time you had consented to retain the information with Getit Stores.  Please note that if you "do not agree" to, or "opt out" from, providing personal or other information requested by us, you may not be able to access certain areas of the Site and/or avail certain Services and/or Indirect Services.  However, it may be noted that Getit Stores reserves the right to send service related and your specific and preferred transaction related communication without offering you the facility to opt-out. You can update your Account Details _(defined below)_ , Personal Information and other information at any time. At your request, Getit Stores can also cancel your registration and remove/block your Personal Information from it's database. However, this information may remain in our archive even after deletion or termination of your account as required by law and the handling of the same is in accordance with the provisions of the applicable law and as intimated by the government agency from time to time. ****

**4.                   ****Use of information for marketing**

In line with any permission given by you to us, we may send you direct marketing communications about our own, or selected third party goods and services and disclose your information to other organizations who may send direct marketing communications to you.  You can change your marketing preferences if you are registered with us.  In addition, you can unsubscribe from email communications via unsubscribe links provided in communications sent to you. ****

**5.                   ****Use of Cookies**

By using Getit Stores, our servers (hosted by a third party service provider) may collect information indirectly and automatically about your activities on the Site by way of cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a site sends to your computer or other media device while you are viewing or interacting with the site.  We use cookies and other such devices to compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our Site and to help us improve the structure of our Site (we cannot identify you personally in this way).  Further it allows us to understand who has seen which pages and advertisements on the Site, to determine how frequently particular such pages and advertisements are visited, to determine the most popular areas of the Site and generally in order to monitor usage of the Site. We may combine your visitor session information or other information collected through cookies and other technical methods with personally identifiable information in order to understand and improve your online experiences and to determine what products, promotions and services you prefer or are likely to be of interest to you. This information is not linked to your Personal Information and is maintained distinctly.

You may also get cookies from our advertisers. We do not control these cookies, and once you have clicked on the advertisement and left the Site, our Privacy Policy no longer applies. Getit Stores is not responsible for collecting cookies through Linked Sites ( _defined below_ ), neither is it liable for misuse of the information you provide to Linked Sites.

It is clarified that we store information only in the manner contained herein and in accordance with the provisions of applicable law.

You can change your web browsers settings to accept or not to accept cookies. Getit Stores may use third-party service providers to serve ads on it's behalf across the internet and sometimes on the Site. Such third party service providers may collect anonymous information about your visits to the Site and the Products available on the Site. Personally identifiable information is not linked to data collected from this source.

Getit Stores could use log file including internet protocol addresses, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyse trends, administer the Site, track user movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. These are not linked to information identifiable personally. ****

**6.                   **Information Sharing

For payments, other than cash on delivery, Getit Stores using online payment gateway operated by third party and the information that you provide at the time of making a purchase on the Site is held and stored with third party payment gateway operator authorised at multiple points. The payment gateway operator may also have access to your online purchase history/details that you make from the Site. These payment gateways are digitally encrypted, thereby providing the highest possible degree of privacy and care available, currently. Whilst we are unable to guarantee hundred percent (100%) security, this makes it hard for a hacker to decrypt your details. You are strongly recommended not to send full credit or debit card details in unencrypted electronic communications with us. Also, you are responsible for protecting against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. We will not be liable for the disclosure and dissemination of Personal Information to third parties which you as prudent Users put up on the Site, and available to the other Users of the Site.

Kindly note that we **do** **not** store extremely sensitive information like your credit card information on our database.

Getit Stores, handles the information only in accordance with the provisions of the applicable law as made applicable from time to time and only for the duration lawfully required, thereunder. Getit Stores may disclose aggregated information, including to aggregators, about the use of the Site without Personal Information. Getit Stores implements standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception of Personal Information. However, Getit Stores feels prudent to inform you that no internet site can fully eliminate security risks and enforcement of privacy laws are at a developing stage in some parts of the world. ****

**7.                   **Storage of Information

Getit Stores does not rent, sell or share your personal or sensitive information and does not disclose any of your Personal Information to third parties unless you have granted Getit Stores the permission to do so.. However, we may pass your Personal Information to other third parties in the following scenarios:

(i)                 To help us process questions you may have about a purchase or service, registration or other inquiry you may have;

(ii)               To confirm or correct what we know about you;

(iii)             We may pass your Personal Information to our employees, contractors, suppliers and/or agents to administer the Services provided to you by us now or in the future;

(iv)             To help us or law enforcement agencies prevent fraud, money laundering, terrorism and other crimes.  Also,  we may disclose your Personal Information to the police, regulatory bodies or legal advisers in connection with any alleged criminal offence or suspected breach of this Privacy Policy and or the breach of other terms and conditions otherwise relating to you or otherwise where required by law and we will co-operate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity of or locate anyone breaching this Privacy Policy or otherwise for the prevention or detection of crime or the apprehension or prosecution of offenders. 

(v)               If you call our customer care call centre, we may pass your Personal Information to our call centre to allow them to deal with your call more efficiently;

(vi)             Assisting an agency in undertaking research for us;

(vii)           If another organization is engaged by us to perform tasks on our behalf, such as delivering goods to you;

(viii)         Compliance with an audit on our business;

(ix)             If we sell all or any part of our business or merge with another company;

(x)               If it is necessary for legal proceedings and when we believe in good faith that any applicable law ,regulation, government, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer requires it or to protect the safety or security of users of the Site;

(xi)             If we use third party processors to administer and process your Personal Information for the purposes notified in the Privacy Policy, e.g. for hosting activities related to the use of the Site or Services; and

(xii)           To obtain advice from third parties such as auditors or legal advisors.

In addition to the above, disclosures may also be made if it was clearly stated at the time of registration and, where required, if you have given permission for this. Generally, we will disclose only the information we consider reasonably necessary to disclose. Also, some general statistical information about the Site user base, sales patterns, traffic volumes and related matters may be passed on to reputable third parties but these details will not include information personally identifying you. 

Further it may be noted that we may share your information with the affiliates of Getit Stores. An affiliate for the purposes of this Privacy Policy shall mean any company in which Getit Stores directly or indirectly holds fifty percent (50 %) or more of the issued share capital (or voting rights) and any subsidiary of such company; or if Getit Stores either directly or indirectly through one or more intermediate persons, controls, is controlled by or is under common control with Getit Stores. For the purposes of this definition, "control" means the power to direct the management or policies of a company, whether through the ownership of over fifty percent (50 %) of the voting power of such company, through the power to appoint over half of the members of the board of directors or similar governing body of such company or through written contractual arrangements. ****

**8.                   **Third Party **Sites**

Please note that this policy does not cover any third party Sites to which we provide links in the Site, nor does it cover advertisers.  They may have their own privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of use. 

Getit Stores provides third-party advertisements and only links to third party sites through the Site ( **"Linked Site")** , but does not provide any Personal Information to these third-party sites or advertisers.

Getit Stores clarifies that the Linked Sites are operated by third parties and are not under control of or affiliation or association of Getit Stores unless specifically expressed by Getit Stores. Getit Stores is not responsible for any form of transmission, material received from any Linked Site. We are not liable and do not represent anything regarding the privacy practices and policies adopted by the Linked Sites and their owners/ operators. Also, we are not in a position to control or guarantee the accuracy, integrity, or quality of the information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, videos, messages or other relevant materials available on the Linked Sites.

Providing the Linked Sites on Getit Stores does not imply or convey any endorsement by Getit Stores in any manner or of the contents of the Linked Site. You are aware that the information you provide on the Linked Sites shall be governed by policies of the Linked Sites which you review. Getit Stores does not have power or authority to prevent misuse of your information through the Linked Sites or advertisers.

Linked Sites and advertisers may use technology to send the advertisements on Getit Stores directly to your browser because of which the Linked Site or advertisers automatically receive your internet protocol address. They may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize advertising content. Getit Stores has no access or control over cookies or other features of the Linked Sites or advertisers and are not governed by this Privacy Policy. ****

**9.                   **Security Practices

Getit Stores strives to ensure the security, integrity protection and privacy of your Personal Information against unauthorized access or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. We follow stringent security techniques and requirements for handling sensitive and personal information. These techniques and requirements are fully compliant with the guidelines set forth under law. Our servers are accessible only to authorized personnel. Your information logged under this Privacy Policy is shared with respective personnel only on need to know basis and/ or for the purpose of completing a transaction and/ or to providing services you have requested. All representatives handling information under these provisions are under contractual confidentiality obligation with Getit Stores. While, we take every step to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, by using this Site, you agree and confirm that Getit Stores is not liable for any disclosure due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties or Linked Sites.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, you must keep account details, including your username and password (" **Account Details** ") confidential at all times, and should not reveal the same to any third parties.  You must take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized disclosure of your Account Details (including logging out from your account at the end of each session), and you must notify us immediately if your Account Details becomes known to any unauthorized user.  You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Account Details, and all activities that occur under your account(s).  Any breach of these terms and conditions by anyone to whom you disclose your account details, including your username and password will be treated as if the breach had been committed by you, and will not relieve you of your obligations under the Terms and Conditions. 

Notwithstanding anything contained herein, Getit Stores shall not be liable for any loss, damage or misuse of your Personal Information due to a force majeure event. A **force majeure event**  for the purposes of this Privacy Policy shall mean any event that is beyond reasonable control of Getit Stores and shall include, without limitation, sabotage, fire, flood, explosion, acts of God, civil commotion, strikes or industrial action of any kind, riots, insurrection, war, acts of government, computer hacking, unauthorised access to computer data and storage device, computer viruses breach of security and encryption or any other cause beyond the control of Getit Stores.. ****

**10.               ****Acceptance to terms**

By registering with Getit Stores and using the Services you are deemed to have agreed to the terms of this Policy. This Policy should be at all times read along with the Terms and Conditions. The Policy applies to all information, including Personal Information and Account Details. 

By using the Services and/or Indirect Services , you agree and acknowledge that your Personal Information may be transferred across national boundaries and stored and processed in any the country around the world. You acknowledge that in the process of providing the Services under the Site, some activities relating to handling of information collected under the Policy may be done by Getit Stores's trusted third party vendors or agents including credit card processors, web hosting providers, communication services, and web analytic providers. ****

**11.               ****Changes to this policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and we will post the latest version on the Site. You are expected to keep visiting the Site and reading the Terms and Conditions and the Policies at regular intervals to keep yourself updated. ****

**12.               ****Amendments to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add or delete portions of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy from time to time, in order to keep track and take note of the changes.  Your use of the Site following any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify and constitute your consent to and acceptance of such revised this Privacy Policy. We will not file or store a copy of these terms for each interaction on transaction by you via the Site. We therefore recommend that you save a copy of this Privacy Policy for future reference, and ensure that such copies can be reliably verified as being effective (i.e. published on the Site) on a particular date. ****

**13.               ****Contact details**

Thank you for reading our Privacy Policy and thank you for choosing our Site as your reliable source of news and views on the internet.  If you have any questions about anything contained in the Privacy Policy, you can email us with any questions, queries or complaints at [[http://support.askmebazaar.com](http://support.askmebazaar.com/)]. ****

**14.               ****Disputes**

Any disputes over inter alia collection, storage and handling of Personal Information will be governed by this Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions and by the laws of India and courts of New Delhi shall have exclusive jurisdiction. For any communication under this Privacy Policy please contact Getit Stores on [http://support.askmebazaar.com](http://support.askmebazaar.com/)
